ODUJOKO ADEGOKE

Professional Summary

Knowledgeable Technical Support Specialist with 3 years of experience in small and large corporations. Eager to share technical know-how and provide service for common operating systems such as Microsoft Windows and Apple macOS, as well as related computer hardware and accessories.

Work History

Technical Support (09/2022-Present) Specialist

GWX LOGISTICS

- Conduct Regular Monitoring and Reviews of system usage to ensure that employees use equipment appropriately.
- Issued and maintained security systems with frequent updates. Could easily troubleshoot issues within 18 hours of identification.
- Developed moderate knowledge of computer repair and maintenance limited to testing machines, devices and equipment to ensure optimal performance.

Technical Support (02/2021-05/2022) Specialist

CREDIT WOLF

- Server implementation and support.
- · Network implementation and Support.
- Ensured Backups are completed in line with company policy.
- Diagnosing hardware and software faults and solve technical and application problems.

Contact

08091246333

Adegoke.works@gmail.com

Education

Bachelor of Science

Bowen University 2016-2020

Diploma in Web Development

New Horizon Central 2020-2021

Skills

- Organized
- Communication
- Teamwork
- Meeting deadlines
- Critical thinking
- Leadership
- Creativity